Omid Esmaelbeyg

Python Developer

Email: omid.delta96@gmail.com

Phone: +989173845466

Summary

Experienced Python developer with history of developing and working on many different projects and sophisticated on both programming and networking and familiar with Linux systems and TCP/IP.

Having experience developing web services and websites using Django framework.

Good team player and a self-learner. Very interested in seeing and experiencing new environments and technologies and getting things done. Positive attitude toward changes and stress and love to solve problems.

.....

Experience

Python/Django Developer, freelancer

2018 - Present

Developing websites using Python and Django framework. Working on many different and challenging projects.

Python Developer, Bahonar Technical College of Shiraz

2017 - 2018

Developed and programmed universities projects that had been assigned me and implemented Artificial Intelligence and Machine Learning into some of that projects.

Shiraz, Fars

Network Engineer, Dataclimber Company

2016 - 2019

Part time job as network engineer alongside my university. Some of my responsibilities were designing and implementing network infrastructures, Configuring and Installing Network services and servers like Active Directory, routing and switching, Linux administrating and etc.

Shiraz, Fars

Education

Associate, Software E	ingineering,	Bahonar	Technical	College of Shiraz
-----------------------	--------------	---------	-----------	-------------------

2014 - 2016

Become second top student in Software Engineering.

Shiraz, Fars

Bachelor's Degree, Software Engineering, Bahonar Technical College of Shiraz

2016 - 2019

Teacher assistant of Network Operating System course.

Shiraz, Fars

Skills

HTML Python

CSS Django

Javascript MangoDB

PostgreSQL MCSA

MySql CCNA

Git Mikrotik (MTCNA)

Bash Scripting Networking
Information Technology Security
Linux(LPIC1, LPIC2) Docker

Languages

English Professional working proficiency

German Elementary proficiency

Persian Native

About Me

 Motivated, dedicated, hardworking, organized, reliable and fast learner person and have good ability to deal with problems.

Flexible and adaptable to any environment and easily assimilate any new technology.

Sociable, a good team player, with good communication skills.

Recognition/respect for people's diversity

Portfolio website: omidesmaelbeyg.ir

LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/omid-esmaelbeyg-483ba6159/

GitHub: https://github.com/omid96

Stackoverflow: https://stackoverflow.com/users/11458812/omid-esmaelbeyg